A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 11, Accession 2022:039 FA1863
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 11, Accession 2022:039
1969-2021
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1863
20.6 Cubic Feet 54 containers: 53 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 11) consists primarily of grant files.
Arrangement
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 11) are arranged as received.
- A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - Adaptive Change Process, 2009-2018 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Albion College - Associate Professor Leadership Program, Great Lakes Colleges Association, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- American Academy of Arts and Sciences - National Commission on Language Learning, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American Academy of Religion - Religion and International Affairs Fellowships, U.S. Department of State, 2015-2019 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- African Antiquarian Society - "Paul Revere: Artisan and Entrepreneur" Exhibition and Catalog, 2015-2021 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- American Council of Learned Societies - Centennial Commemoration, 2016-2018 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- American Council of Learned Societies - China Studies Program, 2013-2017 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- American Council of Learned Societies - China Studies Program, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- American Council of Learned Societies - Launch of China Studies Program, 2010-2017 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- American Council on Education (ACE) - Global Education and Diversity in Higher Education, 2010-2014 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- American Folklore Society - China-U.S. Forum on Intangible Cultural Heritage, 2012-2019 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- American Friends of Prospect Burma - Myanmar-Bangladesh Exchange Program, 2014-2019 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- American Indian College Fund - Film and Media Internships, 2001-2017 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- American Institute for Indonesian Studies - Fellowship Program, 2011-2019 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- American Institute for Indonesian Studies - Programmatic Activities and Scholarly Exchange Program, 2012-2019 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- American Institute for Indonesian Studies - Center Establishment, Jakarta, Indonesia, 2011-2019 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- American Institute of Physics - International Survey of Women in Physics, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- American Philological Association - Summer Classics Seminar Series, 2008-2018 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- American University - Religion and Climate Change in Cross-Regional Perspective, 2003-2019 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Arizona State University Foundation - American Experience Initiative, China, 2014-2019 (Box 3, Folder 20-21, Box 4, Folder 22)
- Art Institue of Chicago - American Silver Collection Digitization, 2002-2021 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Asheville Art Museum - Permanent Collection and Publication, 2016-2021 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Asia Foundation - U.S.-China Relations Education and Exchange Program, 2011-2019 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
- Asia Foundation - China's Foreign NGO Management System Online Information Platform, 1985-2017 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Asia Society - U.S.-China Task Force Project, 1985-2019 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Asia Society - "Buddhist Art of Myanmar" Exhibition and Catalog, 2014-2018 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Asia Society - "ChinaFile" Online Magazine, 2006-2019 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Asian Art Museum of San Francisco - Henry R. Luce Gallery, 1998-2019 (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
- Asian Art Museum of San Francisco - "Emperor's Treasures: Chinese Art from the National Palace Museum, Taipei" Exhibition and Catalog, 1969-2017 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- ASIANetwork - Post-Doctoral Teaching Fellowship Program, 1998-2019 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Aspen Institute - International Issues and Congress, 2001-2018 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Aspen Institute - Extremism and the Iranian Nuclear Negotiations Congressional Conference, 1992-2017 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Aspen Institute - International Issues and Congress, 1992-2017 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Association for Asian Studies - Less Commonly Taught Languages Program, 2017-2019 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Association for Asian Studies - Timor-Leste Studies Initative, 2016-2018 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Association for Asian Studies - Archaeology in Asia, AAS Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, 2013-2018 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Association for Asian Studies - East Asian Studies Librarianship, 2012-2018 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Association for Asian Studies - New Program Initiatives for Annual Meetings, 2010-2018 (Box 7, Folder 43-44)
- Association of Art Museum Directors - Museum Diversity Initiative, United Negro College Fund, 2013-2017 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Association of Art Museum Curators - Annual Conference Travel Grant, 2017-2018 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Association of Gospel Rescue Missions - General Support, 2017-2019 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Association of Historians of American Art - "Panorama" Journal Support, 2005-2021 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Association of Regional Centers for Asian Studies - Chinese Diaspora in Southeast Asia, 2010-2020 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
- Atlantic Monthly Group, Inc. - Religion Coverage on TheAtlantic.com, 2016-2019 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Alice Austen House - Digitization of Photography and Archival Collections, 2013-2019 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Baltimore Museum of Art - "Tomorrow is Another Day" Mark Bradford Exhibition, 2017-2021 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Beijing Civil Society Development Research Center - Bilingual Chinese-English Media Platform (China Development Brief), 2015-2019 (Box 9, Folder 54-57)
- Birmingham Museum of Art - "The Original Makers: Folk Art from the Cargo Collection" Exhibition and Catalog, 2017-2019 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Black Mountain College Museum and Arts Center - Catalog and Digitization of Collection, 2017-2019 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Boise Art Museum - "Weather or Not" and "Tall Tales" Exhibitions, 2012-2018 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Bolder Giving, Zing Foundation - President's Pledge Against Global Poverty, 2012-2017 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Bolder Giving - President's Pledge Against Global Poverty, 2011-2018 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Boston University - Religious Pluralism and Civic Peace in Multicultural Societies, 2010-2017 (Box 10, Folder 63-65)
- Bread for the World - Hunger Report, Fragile Environments, Resilient Communities, 2016-2018 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Bronx Museum of the Arts - "Anarchitecture: Gordon Matta-Clark and the Bronx" Exhibition and Catalog, 2007-2021 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Brookings Institution - Rethinking Political Islam: Islamist Responses to a Changing Political Landscape, 2005-2018 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Brown University - Faith, Politics, and Morality Graphic Novel and Digital Project, 2015-2017 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- BYKids - FILMSBYKIDS, Season Two, 2017-2019 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Carnegie Council - "Building Pacific Communities," Global Ethics Network, 2015-2019 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - "The Rise of 'New' Sectarianism in the Middle East", 2014-2018 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Catalogue for Philanthropy - "Directories" Website Development Project, 2012-2019 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Center for American Progress - United States-China Cooperation in Southeast Asia, 2014-2019 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Center for American Progress - United States-China Dialogue on the G-20, 2007-2019 (Box 12, Folder 75-76)
- Center for Effective Philanthropy - 2018 Membership, 2018-2019 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- Center for Effective Philanthropy - 2017 Membership, 2017-2019 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- Center for Effective Philanthropy - 2016 Membership, 2016-2019 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- China Dialogue Trust - China's Global Environmental Impact, 2012-2018 (Box 12, Folder 80-81)
- China Dialogue Trust - China's Global Environmental Impact, 2012-2014 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Corning Museum of Glass - American Glass Collection Research and Digitization, 2015-2021 (Box 13, Folder 83)
- Council of Independent Colleges - Future of Liberal Arts Symposium, Johns Hopkins School of Advanced International Studies, 2010-2011 (Box 13, Folder 84)
- Council of Independent Colleges - Scholarships to Attend the Presidents Institute, 2009-2010 (Box 13, Folder 85)
- CRDF Global - United States-Democratic People's Republic of Korea Scientific Engagement Consortium, 2010-2019 (Box 13, Folder 86-87)
- CRDF Global - United States-Democratic People's Republic of Korea Scientific Engagement Consortium - State Academy of Sciences DPR Korea (Box 13, Folder 86)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
- Danforth Art - Meta Fuller Collection, 2015-2020 (Box 13, Folder 88)
- Denver Art Museum - "Women of Abstract Expressionism" Exhibition and Catalog, 2015-2018 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- Detroit Institute of Arts - "Frederic Church: To the Holy Land and Beyond" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2018 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- Dia Art Foundation - "Sculpture as Place: Carl Andre, A Perspective 1958-2009" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2019 (Box 14, Folder 91)
- Documentary Educational Resources - "Syria in Black and White - 2003" Book Project, 2015-2019 (Box 14, Folder 92)
- Duke University - Liberal Arts Education in China, 2015-2018 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- Duke University - Southeast Asia Research Group Conferences, 2014-2017 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- East-West Center - Southeast Asia Fellowship Program, 2006-2018 (Box 15, Folder 95)
- The Sylvia Bozeman and Rhonda Hughes EDGE Foundation - Expansion and Mentioning Program for Women, Underrepresented Minorites Pursuing Careers, 2015-2017 (Box 15, Folder 96)
- Emory University - The Global Skills Initiative for Graduate Education, 2016-2019 (Box 15, Folder 97)
- Faith Matters, Inc. - God and Government Public Radio Series, 2016-2019 (Box 15, Folder 98)
- Faith Matters, Inc. - God and Government: Religion and State in Fourteen Nations, 2012-2018 (Box 15, Folder 99)
- Faith Matters, Inc. - God and Government: Religion and State in Fourteen Nations, 2013-2018 (Box 15, Folder 100)
- The Field Museum - Cyrus Tang Hall of China Digital Catalog, 2014-2018 (Box 15, Folder 101)
- Figge Art Museum - "William L. Hawkins: An Imaginative Geography" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2020 (Box 16, Folder 102)
- Filmmakers Collaborative - Touching Home in China: In Search of Missing Girlhoods Project, 2014-2019 (Box 16, Folder 103)
- Flint Institute of Arts - Storage for Large-Scale Paintings, 2013-2017 (Box 16, Folder 104)
- Florida International University Foundation, Inc. - Leadership Fellows Program, 2014-2018 (Box 16, Folder 105)
- The Foundation Center - 2018 Membership, 2018-2019 (Box 16, Folder 106)
- The Foundation Center - 2017 Membership, 2017-2019 (Box 16, Folder 107)
- The Foundation Center - 2016 Membership, 2016-2019 (Box 16, Folder 108)
- The Foundation Center - 2015 Membership, 2015-2019 (Box 16, Folder 109)
- The Foundation Center - 2014 Membership, 2014-2019 (Box 16, Folder 110)
- The Foundation Center - 2013 Membership, 2013-2019 (Box 16, Folder 111)
- The Foundation Center - 2012 Membership, 2011-2019 (Box 16, Folder 112)
- The Foundation Center - 2011 Membership, 2010-2019 (Box 16, Folder 113)
- The Foundation Center - 2009, 2010 Membership, 2007-2019 (Box 16, Folder 114)
- Foundation for the National Archives - Federal Hall National Memorial Project, 2007-2018 (Box 17, Folder 115)
- Freer Gallery of Art and Arthur M. Sackler Gallery - Petrography Workshop, Angkor Ceramics Unit, Cambodia, 2016-2019 (Box 17, Folder 116)
- Freer Gallery of Art and Arthur M. Sackler Gallery - Chinese Painting Conservator Position, 2013-2017 (Box 17, Folder 117)
- The Frick Collection - Patronage of American Art Symposium, 2017 (Box 17, Folder 118)
- Friends of the British Council - Bridging Voices Workshop, 2015-2017 (Box 17, Folder 119)
- Friends of the British Council - Bridging Voices, 2012-2018 (Box 17, Folder 120-121)
  Scope and Contents
  Series of transatlantic scholarly and policy dialogues on religion and international affairs.
- Fuller Craft Museum - Digital Catalog of Permanent Collection, 2016-2020 (Box 17, Folder 122)
- Gadjah Mada University - Graduate Student Exchange Program on Inter-Religious and Cross-Cultural Understanding, 2011-2019 (Box 18, Folder 123-124)
- George Mason University Foundation - Russian and Soviet Perspectives on Islam, 2011-2019 (Box 18, Folder 125)
- George Washington University - Tibet Governance Project, 2016-2019 (Box 18, Folder 126)
- George Washington University - Religion and International Affairs in Central Eurasia and Islamic Civil Society, 2016-2019 (Box 18, Folder 127)
- George Washington University - Trilateral Academic Dialogue on the Asia-Pacific Future, 2014-2019 (Box 19, Folder 128)
- George Washington University - Islam in a Changing Middle East, 2013-2018 (Box 19, Folder 129)
- Georgetown University - Religion and Global Development, 2013-2018 (Box 19, Folder 130)
- Georgetown University - Religion, United States Foreign Policy, and Global Development, 2008-2018 (Box 19, Folder 131)
- Georgia Museum of Art, University of Georgia - "Vernacular Modernism: The Photography of Doris Ulmann" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2019 (Box 19, Folder 132)
- J. Paul Getty Trust - "Cave Temples of Dunhuang: Buddhist Art on China's Silk Road" Exhibition and Catalog, 2015-2017 (Box 20, Folder 133-134)
- Gettysburg College - Civil War Era Studies Program, 2015-2018 (Box 20, Folder 135)
- Guggenheim Museum - "The Third Mind: American Artists Contemplate Asia, 1860-1989" Exhibition and Catalog, 2008-2010 (Box 20, Folder 136)
- Hammer Museum - "Jimmie Durham: At the Center of the World" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2019 (Box 20, Folder 137)
- Harvard Art Museum - "The Philosophy Chamber: Harvard's Lost Collection, 1766-1820", 2016-2021 (Box 20, Folder 138)
- Harvard Art Museum - Maneuvers Project, 2015-2018 (Box 21, Folder 139)
  Graduate workshop on art and artmaking.
- Harvard Divinity School - Religious Literacy, Local Leadership in Humanitarian Action, 2016-2018 (Box 21, Folder 140)
- Harvard Law School - SHARIAsource, 2015-2018 (Box 21, Folder 141-142)
  An online portal of resources on Islamic law.
- Harvard University - China Biographical Database Project, 2011-2017 (Box 21, Folder 143)
- Harwood Museum, University of New Mexico - "Mabel Dodge Luhan and Company: American Moderns and the West" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2017 (Box 21, Folder 144)
- High Museum of Art - American Art Collection Digitization, 2014-2017 (Box 21, Folder 145)
- High Museum of Art - "Rising Up: Hale Woodruff's Murals at Talladega College" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2021 (Box 22, Folder 146)
- Human Rights Watch - Religious Intolerance in Southeast Asia and Central Asia, 2014-2017 (Box 22, Folder 147)
- The Huntington Library - "Garden, Art and Commerce in Chinese Woodblock Prints" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2017 (Box 22, Folder 148)
- The Independent Feature Project, Inc. - The Destruction of Memory Film, 2015-2017 (Box 22, Folder 149)
- Indiana University - Philanthropy in China, 2013-2015 (Box 23, Folder 150-151)
- Indiana University - The History of Western Medicine in China, 1800-1950, 2011-2019 (Box 23, Folder 152)
- Indiana University - China and Global Government, Research Center for Chinese Politics and Business, 2010-2017 (Box 23, Folder 153-154)
- Institute of Contemporary Art, Miami - "Infinity is Always Less Than One" Exhibition and Catalog, 2017-2020 (Box 24, Folder 155)
- Institute of International Education - Connecting with the World: International Relations at Higher Education Institutions in Myanmar Program, 2013-2016 (Box 24, Folder 156)
- International Center for Journalists - Online Courses and Joint Reporting Projects on Religion, 2012-2017 (Box 24, Folder 157-158)
- International Center for Religion and Diplomacy - Global Religious Conflict, 2007-2019 (Box 24, Folder 159)
- International Crisis Group - Religion and Conflict in Africa, Asia, and the Middle East, 2015-2018 (Box 25, Folder 160)
- International Crisis Group - Religion and Conflict in Africa and Asia, 2013-2017 (Box 25, Folder 161)
- Ithaka Harbors, Inc. - Asian Studies, 2017-2018 (Box 25, Folder 162)
- Ithaka Harbors, Inc. - Library Support Services for Asian Studies, 2012-2018 (Box 25, Folder 163)
- Japan Center for International Exchange - United States-Japan Women Legislators Dialogue, 2016-2018 (Box 25, Folder 164)
- Japan Society, Inc. - "In the Wake: Japanese Photographers Respond to 3/11" Exhibition, 2016-2017 (Box 25, Folder 165)
- The Jewish Museum - "Married to American Art: Edith Gregor Halpert and the Downtown Gallery" Exhibition and Catalog, 2017-2021 (Box 26, Folder 166)
- KCETLink - LinkAsia News, 2013-2018 (Box 26, Folder 167-168)
- Kemper Museum of Contemporary Art - American Art Collection Digitization, 2016-2019 (Box 26, Folder 169)
- Leiden University - Southeast Asia Neighborhoods Network, 2016-2019 (Box 26, Folder 170)
- Library of Congress - Orientation Seminar, 113th Congress, 2012-2018 (Box 26, Folder 171)
- Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service - Orientation Seminar, 114th Congress, 2014-2018 (Box 27, Folder 172)
- Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service - Orientation Seminar, 114th Congress - CRS at 100: Opening Remarks, How Congress Functions, 2014 July 16 (Box 27, Folder 172)
- Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service - Orientation Seminar, 114th Congress - CRS at 100: The Arab Spring, The Global Economy, 2014 July 16 (Box 27, Folder 172)
- Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service - Orientation Seminar, 114th Congress - CRS at 100: Demography as Destiny, Analysis and Legislative Power, 2014 July 16 (Box 27, Folder 172)
- Long Island University - George Polk Awards in Journalism, 2013-2018 (Box 27, Folder 173)
- Lontar Foundation - Indonesian Poetry and Short Stories, 2013-2019 (Box 27, Folder 174-175)
- Madison Square Park Conservancy - 2016 Art Program and Martin Puryear Installation, 2015-2017 (Box 27, Folder 176)
- Madison Square Park Conservancy - 2015 Art Program, 2014-2021 (Box 27, Folder 177)
- Magnum Foundation - Visual Documentary Projects on Religion in International Affairs, 2016-2017 (Box 28, Folder 178-179)
- Maria Mitchell Association - Women in Science Award, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 180)
- Mark Morris Dance Group - Silk Road Ensemble, Layla and Majnun, 2016-2017 (Box 28, Folder 181)
- The Maureen and Mike Mansfield Foundation - "Rule of Law: Vietnam and the TPP" Project, 2015-2019 (Box 28, Folder 182)
- McGill University - Collaborative Research by Artists and Scholars, 2016-2018 (Box 28, Folder 183)
- Mercy Corps - National Committee on North Korea, 2015-2017 (Box 28, Folder 184)
- Mercy Corps - National Committee on North Korea, 2014-2017 (Box 28, Folder 185)
- Mead Art Museum, Amherst College - "Dimensions Manifesto: Modern Art in the Age of Einstein" Exhibition and Catalog, 2017-2021 (Box 29, Folder 186)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art - "Thomas Cole's Journey: Atlantic Crossings" Exhibition and Catalog, 2017-2019 (Box 29, Folder 187)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art - "Marsden Hartley's Maine" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2018 (Box 29, Folder 188)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art - "Age of Empires: Chinese Art of the Qin and Han Dynasties (221 BC-AD 220)" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2018 (Box 29, Folder 189)
- Michigan State University - "Quilts of Southern China" Exhibition, 2015-2019 (Box 29, Folder 190)
- Minneapolis Institute of Arts - Ancient Chinese Bronzes Exhibition, 2013-2019 (Box 29, Folder 191)
- Montclair Art Museum - "Matisse and American Art" Exhibition and Catalog, 2014-2018 (Box 30, Folder 192)
- The Morgan Library and Museum - "Henry James and American Art" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2019 (Box 30, Folder 193)
- Museum of Modern Art - "Donald Judd" Exhibition and Catalog, 2014-2021 (Box 30, Folder 194-195)
- Nasher Museum of Art, Duke University - "Archibald Motley: Jazz Age Modernist" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2021 (Box 30, Folder 196)
- National Academy of Sciences - Women's Adventures in Science, 2005-2018 (Box 30, Folder 197)
- National Committee on American Foreign Policy - Forum on Asia-Pacific Security, 2016-2019 (Box 31, Folder 198-199)
- National Committee on American Foreign Policy - Forum on Asia-Pacific Security, 2013-2017 (Box 31, Folder 200-201)
- National Committee on United States-China Relations - Public Intellectuals Program, 2011-2019 (Box 32, Folder 202)
- National Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. - "Alfred Stieglitz: The Key Set", 2017-2021 (Box 32, Folder 203)
- National Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. - Corcoran Gallery Art Collection, 2015-2017 (Box 32, Folder 204)
- National Geographic Society - Young Explorers Program, Asia Projects, 2012-2019 (Box 32, Folder 205-206)
- National Humanities Center - Founders Online Website, 2014-2019 (Box 32, Folder 207)
- National Humanities Center - Fact-Finding Trip to China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan, 2012-2019 (Box 32, Folder 208)
- National Trust for Historic Preservation - Historic Artists' Homes and Studios Program, 2016-2021 (Box 33, Folder 209)
- New America - International Reporting Project Fellowship on Religion and International Affairs, 2016-2018 (Box 33, Folder 210)
- The New School - Everyday Religion and Sustainable Environments in the Himalaya, 2010-2017 (Box 33, Folder 211-212)
- New Britain Museum of American Art, Inc. - Digitization of Permanent Collection, 2012-2017 (Box 33, Folder 213)
- New England Foundation for the Arts - Center Stage Pakistan, 2016-2017 (Box 33, Folder 214)
- New Museum - Marcia Tucker Publication, 2015-2019 (Box 34, Folder 215)
- The New School, India China Institute - Sacred Landscapes and Sustainable Futures in the Himalaya, 2014-2018 (Box 34, Folder 216-217)
- New York University - Religion and Politics in America, 2013-2017 (Box 34, Folder 218)
- New York Urban League - STEM Engagement Initiative, 2014-2017 (Box 34, Folder 219)
- Norton Museum of Art - "New Women: Four New York Modernists, 1910-1935" Exhibition and Catalog, 2014-2017 (Box 34, Folder 220)
- NUS American Foundation, Inc. - Religion and NGOs in Asia, 2014-2018 (Box 35, Folder 221-222)
- Pacific Basin Institute - Digital Preservation of the Archive, 2001-2017 (Box 35, Folder 223)
- Parrish Art Museum - "John Graham: Maverick Modernist" Exhibition and Catalog, 2015-2018 (Box 35, Folder 224)
- Partners for Sacred Places - Assessment of the Study of Sacred Places, 2015-2017 (Box 35, Folder 225)
- Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - "World War I and American Art" Exhibition and Catalog, 2015-2019 (Box 35, Folder 226)
- Pennsylvania State University - Assessing Women and Men in Engineering (AWE) Project, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 227)
- Philadelphia Museum of Art - "American Watercolor in the Age of Homer and Sargent" Exhibition and Catalog, 2016-2018 (Box 36, Folder 228)
- Philanthropy New York - 2018 Membership, 2018-2019 (Box 36, Folder 229)
- Philanthropy New York - 2017 Membership, 2017-2019 (Box 36, Folder 230)
- Philanthropy New York - 2016 Membership, 2016-2019 (Box 36, Folder 231)
- Philanthropy New York - 2015 Membership, 2015-2019 (Box 36, Folder 232)
- Philanthropy New York - 2013 Membership, 2013-2019 (Box 36, Folder 233)
- Philanthropy New York - 2012 Membership, 2012-2019 (Box 36, Folder 234)
- Philanthropy New York - 2011 Membership, 2011-2019 (Box 36, Folder 235)
- Philanthropy New York - 2009 Membership, 2009-2019 (Box 36, Folder 236)